Exit Art "Reactions" exhibit collection
Prints & Photographs Division, Library of Congress
- Maxey, Marie
  - [Untitled], photoshop digital image collage; 1444; 917; Skeleton in bottle
- Maxwell, Brookie
  - [Untitled], pariscraft, ink, stamps, envelope; 1445; 62
- Mayberry, Jessica
  - [Untitled], 1446; 2152; Email
- Mayer, Aline
  - The Day After, 1447; 1417; Dark undefined rectangular image
- Mayers, Natasha
  - Twin Tragedy, color copy of ink on paper; 1448; 435; Two figures
- de Marchena, Edmundo
  - [Untitled], mixed media; 1449; 1605; Drawings and handwritten text over plane ticket confirmation
- Mayfield, Mary Lou
  - [Untitled], 1450; 2288; My office is in Newark...
- Mbole Epie, Rose
  - America Is Hurting And So Are We, poem; 1451; 2130; Oh how twisted the minds...
- McAllister, Justin
  - [Untitled], 1452; 706
- McBride, Seth
  - End, photograph; 1453; 2050; Out of focus photograph
- McCabe, Richard
  - Box Cutter, ink on paper; 1454; 1130; Line drawing of a box cutter on white paper
- McCabe, Taryn O'Dwyer
  - Void of Home, 1455; 503
- McCabe, Dudley Mary
  - [Untitled], oil paper; 1456; 617; Crow
- McCalebb, Howard
  - Depression?, mixed media; 1457; 1266; Text on depression "Depression? Depression is an illness that can be treated effectively."
- McCann, Kimmy
  - After Normal, 1458; 472
- McCarter D.
  - [Untitled], 1462; 1398; Collaged words: help, war, terrorism, etc.
- McCarter, D.
  - [Untitled], 1463; 1399; WTC burning
- McCarter, D.
  - [Untitled], 1464; 1400; WTC w/"United We Stand"
- McCarter D.
  - [Untitled], drawing; 1465; 1401; Smiley sun w/WTC
- McCarten, D.
  - [Untitled], pencil on paper; 1466; 1402
- McCarter, D.
  - [Untitled], 1467; 1403; By Annabel Fowler
- McCarter, D.
  - [Untitled], 1468; 1405; Flag and "don't hate"
- McCarter, D.
  - [Untitled], pencil drawing; 1469; 1404; With swirls
- McCloskey, Tom
  - The Stoker, 1470; 1221
- McConaughy, Claire
  - [Untitled], 1471; 811; Images of petals
- McConville, Shayna
  - [Untitled], 1472; 341; 1 of 2 watercolor drawings
- McConville, Shayna
  - [Untitled], watercolor drawings; 1473; 342; 2 of 2
- McCormack, Dan
  - [Untitled], 1474; 215
- McCormick, Shane
  - [Untitled], 1475; 667; Workman street photograph
- McDonald, Alison
  - [Untitled], photograph; 1476; 2100; Photo of woman holding camera w/particle mask
- McDonald, Alison
  - [Untitled], photograph; 1477; 2101; Photo of two people crossing the street w/particle masks on and Mickey Mouse heads behind them
- McDonald, Alison
  - [Untitled], photograph; 1478; 2102; Photo of 5 Asian men turned away from the camera looking at newspaper postings on wall
- McDowell, Richard
  - [Untitled], color photo; 1478b; 3209
- McElroy, Terry
  - [Untitled], 1479; 1851
- McGibbon, Dan
  - [Untitled], 1480; 1340; Firefighters and flag
- McKeown, Anne Queeney
  - What words, relief print on handmade paper; 1481; 800
- McLaughlin, Patricia M.
  - [Untitled], 1482; 1113; Little figures
- McLean, Courtney
  - Dear U.S.A., over the summer a tragic event changed my life..., letter; 1483; 398
- McLean, Kathryn
  - [Untitled], 1484; 201; 'For Now" "I am my brother's keeper..."
- Mcleleh, Mary
  - [Untitled], digital image; 1485; 813; Image of a dartboard with text on it and skulls around the edge
- McLoughlin, Mark
  - End of World Courtesy Notice, 1486; 965; Sorry! You weren't home
- McNeal, Meridith
  - Namaste: The Divine in Me Bows To The Divine in You (Detail), painted Sanskrit text on 7000 rose petals; 1487; 729
- McPherson, Dorothy
  - Reactions, poem; 1489; 2267; Oh blindness to...
- McPherson, Dorothy
  - REACTIONS, 1490; 3081; Oh blindness
- McQueen, Kathleen
  - Notes from 9/11, text on paper; 1491; 796; Essay poem on paper
- Meagher, Patrick
  - [Untitled], photograph; 1492; 1814
- Meetal, Julie
  - Scream, 1493; 1343; Skull
- Meledandri, Nina
  - Skeleton Series II, 1494; 637; Cross-hatch
- Merhi, Yucef
  - WTC I, 1497; 962
- Merrill, Dan
  - I, You, He, She, We, You, They, 1498; 623; "I, You, He"
- Mesches, Arnold
  - [Untitled], 1499; 2043; Plane and figures in masks
- Metzman, Helen Lowe
  - Life is Short, text on Paper; 1500; 779; Poem
- Meyers, Charles
  - [Untitled], drawing and poetry; 1501; 20; Dropped off in person--2 submissions
- Meyers, Charles
  - [Untitled], drawing and poetry; 1502; 21; Dropped off in person--2 submissions
- Meyers, Roberta
  - Editor's Page, 1505; 871
- Michael, Creighton
  - [Untitled], photocopy; 1506; 936; Directions to WTC
- Michel, Howard & Francine Prose
  - Easy Spirit, painting; 1506b; 1631; Pigeons on dusty windowsill with "easy spirit" written below
- Micros, Nick
  - [Untitled], 1507; 423
- Miele
  - [Untitled], pencil on paper; 1508; 1256; Abstract handwriting
- Migliore, Bartolomeo
  - [Untitled], 1509; 305; Drawing
- Milgrom, Lilianne
  - [Untitled], graphite and wax pencil; 1510; 850; Woman with head in hair
- Miller, Jane
  - [Untitled], 1511; 1004; Black silouette of a man standing on right side of page
- Miller, Judith S.
  - [Untitled], 1512; 304; Loss
- Miller, Marjorie
  - [World Trade Center Twin Towers during the September 11th terrorist attack, New York City], photographic print; 1513; 2197; Tower with starburst
- Miller, Stephen Paul
  - [Untitled], poem; 1514; 3053
- Miller, Stephen Paul
  - [Untitled], poem; 1515; 3054
- Miller, Stephen Paul
  - [Untitled], poem; 1516; 3055
- Miller, Stephen Paul
  - [Untitled], poem; 1517; 3056
- Miller, Stephen Paul
  - [Untitled], poem; 1518; 3057
- Miller, Stephen Paul
  - [Untitled], poem; 1519; 3058
- Miller, Steve
  - [Untitled], artwork; 1520; 93; Via mail www.stevemiller.com
- Minot, Virginia
  - Fragments, 1521; 2233; Glass
- Minsky, Tequila
  - Dec. 11 -3 Months Later, photograph; 1522; 1071; Close-up photograph of Rudy Guiliani
- Minter, Marilyn
  - [Untitled], photograph; 1523; 1065; Close ip photo of someone with a cigarette in their mouth and their hand to their face as if in dismay
- Minter-Forster, Myrna
  - First Explosion, 1524; 1544
- Mitchell, Samantha
  - Jersey City, NJ Sept. 11, 2001, photograph; 1525; 1385; Photograph of cars and trucks in traffic under a large cloud filled sky
- Mitchell, Samantha
  - Mask Sept. 17, 2001, photograph; 1526; 1384; Man wearing a particle mask on a NYC street
- Mitchell, Samantha
  - New York Stock Exchange Sept. 17, 2001, photograph; 1527; 1383; View of NYSE from sidewalk; back view of GI in center
- Mitchell, Samantha
  - Route 3 East Sept. 11, 2001, photograph; 1528; 1382; Cars parked in front of fence with WTC burning in background
- Mlo, Sabrina
  - [Untitled], 1529; 1554
- Moe, Benjamin
  - [Untitled], 1531; 1757; Towers w/time
- Mohr, Jack N.
  - Fingerprints, Fireholes, digital print of collage, fingerpaints, firehandles; 1532; 1358; Collage with dove shapes
- Mojaven, Paul
  - [Untitled], 1533; 1975; Open ims
- Mojaven, Paul
  - [Untitled], computer art; 1533b; 3287
- Mojzsis, K.
  - [Untitled], print on paper; 1534; 1389; Large dark circle
- Mola, Kelly
  - [Untitled], 1535; 1550; Robot
- Mola, Kelly
  - [Untitled], 1536; 1772; Why i love ny
- Moldi, Ravenna, Cristiana
  - [Untitled], 1538; 1989
- Mon, Bascha
  - Exploding Heart, encaustic and collage; 1539; 1335; Encaustic and collage
- Monaghan & Schaub, Katie & James
  - [Untitled], ferropremere and gouache on arches paper; 1540; 1560; Dark abstract design
- Montano, Linda
  - Silence, poem; 1541; 9; One word "SILENCE"
- Montano, Linda
  - silent heart, poem; 1542; 2162
- Montano, Linda
  - Pray, poem; 1543; 10; One word "PRAY"
- Montgomery, Mike
  - Where Were You?, text on paper; 1544; 829; WWW.strengthmag.com
- Mood, Alexander
  - [Untitled], 1545; 1998; Man reading newspaper
- Mooney, Chris
  - American Punk, 1546; 1997; Black flag button
- Moore, Lea
  - Eggshell Mosaic, 1547; 1165; Now where
- Moore, Lea
  - [Untitled], 1548; 1166; Hugging firemen
- Moore, Lea
  - [Untitled], 1549; 1167; Crying fireman
- Moore, Lea
  - [Untitled], 1550; 1168; Fireman face
- Moore, Steve
  - A Blessing of Healing, conte crayon (sanguine) and olive oil on rice paper; 1552; 981; Image of a cross on rice paper with translucent red and orange squares over it
- Moorehead, Katrina
  - [Untitled], 1553; 297; "Ideal Total Now"
- Moren, Lisa
  - [Untitled], 1555; 252; Email, "Oh, I am so glad you joined..."
- Morgan, Arnetta
  - [Untitled], ink on paper; 1556; 1267; Line drawing of a ground with flowers in it and a smoke filled sky
- Morgan, Robert
  - [Untitled], 1557; 3021; Via email
- Moriarty, Dan & Mary
  - Your Hands, poem; 1559; 2121
- Morrison, Mandy
  - [Untitled], 1560b; 3281; Copy of visitor id of WTC
- Morrow
  - [Untitled], 1561; 1043; Big eyes
- Marrow, Gina
  - [Untitled], 1562; 207; Part of group of students of the Hudson School
- Moscariello, Jaye
  - [Untitled], 1563; 1976; Naked woman holding globe
- Moscariello, Jaye
  - [Untitled], 1564; 3035
- Moseni, Arezoo
  - [Untitled], 1565; 384; Triangle image
- Moss-Vreeland, Patricia
  - [Untitled], 1567; 1454; 9 line poem in different fonts
- Mroivili, Ali
  - [Untitled], 1568; 1944; 3 tube towers
- Muchaypina, Jose
  - Endure the Elements, 1569; 1513; Shapes made of dots
- Mulea, DiAnna
  - [Untitled], 1571; 30; Sent via email--text w/photo--Bibi needs to print photo for looseleaf
- Mullen, Maureen
  - The 2nd Day of Kindergarten, 1572; 751; Part of "Body of Knowledge" series. Flower image in lower left hand corner with tornado going up center
- Munroe, Scott A.
  - The Father of Zero-Tolerance (A. Hitler), colored pencil; 1573; 727; Image of Adolph Hitler holding a chain and text at top of page
- Munson, Portia
  - [Untitled], 1574; 1872; Stones
- Mur-Ray, Ming
  - [Untitled], 1575; 1622; "during my recent visit"
- Mur-Ray, Ming
  - [Untitled], 1576; 1623; Photo of Rio
- Murdock, Annie
  - [Untitled], digital image; 1577; 1388; Abstract burst of light in dark background
- Murdoch, Zoe
  - [Untitled], mixed media; 1578; 1488; Collage of newsprint and drawings
- Murphy, Jennifer
  - Exegesis, folded, burnt, and collaged paper, wire, vase, wooden shelf; 1579; 1260; Wall installation photo
- Murphy, Kellie
  - Self portrait, photographic print; 1580; 414; Cupped hands
- Murphy, Natasha
  - [Untitled], 1581; 259; Letter from schoolteacher, Ms. Murphy
- Murray, SyliAnn
  - Thru the Fire, poem; 1582; 3071
- Murray, SylviAnn
  - 9/11-Feeling the Pain, 1583; 3095
- Murray, SylviAnn
  - Weaponized Anthrax, 1584; 1752; Gas mask
- Murray, SylviAnn
  - Hope Emerges: Cat Found Alive in Rubble!, 1585; 1753; Street with cat
- Murray, SylviAnn
  - 9/11 Attack, 1586; 1754
- Musicmaster
  - [Untitled], 1589; 218; Poem/drawing 1 of 3
- Musicmaster
  - [Untitled], 1590; 219; Poem/drawing 2 of 3
- Musicmaster
  - [Untitled], 1591; 220; Poem/drawing 3 of 3
- Muslin, Lee
  - A Rising, 1592; 674
- N'Cognita, Vernita
  - [Untitled], 1595; 1795; Trying to reach you.
- Nachtsheim, Norma
  - [Untitled], 1596; 1000; Henceforth Arts Studio. Abstracted image of wreckage of towers
- Nagasaki, Y.
  - Just Routine Heroism (Ground Zero, NYC 2001), c-print; 1597; 1573; Photo of four firefighters holding up American flag at ground zero
- Nakajima, Yukari
  - [Untitled], 1598; 569; "as the moon..."
- Nakamura, Keichi
  - [Untitled], digital image; 1599; 1548; Mail is not weapons
- Nakaye, Melanie
  - [Untitled], 1600; 1182; Man and animal with shadows
- Namekawa, Misa
  - Fragile Art, photograph of plaster sculpture; 1601; 1527; Broken plaster statue of liberty
- Namenwirth, Aron
  - [Untitled], digital image; 1602; 999; Image of a crowd of people walking over a bridge
- Nash, Amy
  - [Untitled], 1603; 3005; Attached is a poem I wrote..
- Nash, Damian
  - [Untitled], 3 page poem; 1604; 2169; 3 page poem, "To do this we must all open..."
- Nash, Damien
  - [Untitled], poem; 1605; 2169; To do this...(3 pages)
- Nebeska, Eva
  - [Untitled], 1606; 894; Painting on photo of Prague
- Nechvatal, Joseph
  - My Reaction to 9_11, 1607; 191; Prose
- Nehmad, Deborah Gottheil
  - [Untitled], pyrography and embossment on paper; 1608; 714; Squares
- Neustein, Alex
  - American Flag With 3187 Stars, wax ink print on paper; 1609; 1023; This piece is based on the motif of a flag of the United States. The flag is displayed in portrait alignment, with the blue square on the upper-left hand corner. The flag has been modified such that instead of 50 stars, there are 3,187 stars
- Nevarez, Julia
  - [Untitled], color pencil; 1610; 854; Arrows
- Newby, Nedra
  - [Untitled], 1611; 1613; Floorplan of WTC
- Newman, Daniel
  - ABORT, 1612; 1535; Plain sheet of paper with ABORT written on it
- Newman, Jeremy
  - [Untitled], 1613; 665; Flag and profile of figures
- Newman, Mendy
  - Survival?, 1614; 1206; Survival delivery service
- Nhlengethwa, Goodness
  - [Untitled], color print; 1614b; 3300; Photo tree branch and water covered with text
- Nicholas, Suzanne
  - Lived An Extraordinary Life, Died An Extraordinary Death, 1615; Shoes
- Nichols, Tucker
  - [Untitled], 1616; 406; What
- Nieto, Ignacio
  - Lo Que Usted Nunca Supo del Dia 11...!, 1617; 2008; Airplane in sky, newspaper layout
- Niffenegger, Carol J.
  - Valley of Decision, mixed media; 1618; 1371; 5 stanza poem in black text
- Nimmer, Dean
  - [Untitled], 1619; 2116; Small photo
- Nishyama, Jiro
  - [Untitled], drawing; 1620; 789; Small sailboatin sky above water
- Nixon, Kate
  - [Untitled], 1621; 672; Clocks
- Noble, Kevin
  - [Untitled], 1622; 1530; Press Conference at New York City Hall in support of Israeli control of Jerusalem. January 11, 2001
- North, Hilary
  - How My Life Has Changed, 1623; 188
- Novak, Justin
  - [Untitled], digital image; 1624; 1422; Close up photo of a hand giving the peace sign resembling twin towers
- Nyland, Steven
  - [Untitled], photo; 1625; 1601
- Nzimz
  - [Untitled], graphite pencil and colored pencil on yellow tracing paper; 1626; 3070
- Olson, Richard
  - [Untitled], crayon on paper; 1627; 2016; Red streajk across middle, intersected with two thick, black lines
- O'Connor, Gary
  - [Untitled], 1629; 1137; Blurred words
- O'Regan, Dave
  - [Untitled], 1630; 432; "The Taliban Times"
- Oatis, Leah
  - [Untitled], oversized photo and text; 1632; 699
- Ockert Hai, Eloise
  - [Untitled], pen on paper; 1633; 1449; Long handwritten essay
- Oh, Hyeobjoon
  - Mercy, 1634; 1850; Compact design-y
- Oisteanu, Valery
  - WTC Blood Stained Flags, print of collage; 1635; 259
- Oizechowski, M.
  - Innocence Replaced by Anger and Fear, page of text; 1636; 1119
- Oizechowski, M.
  - Terror..Grief..Loss..Terror..War..Death..Terror, 1637; 1118; Grieving/Two Important Questions/Evil on a Daily Basis
- Oizechowski, M.
  - [Untitled], 1638; 1115; Puzzle
- Ojo, Jide
  - The Song of New York, mixed media; 1639; 1854; Head of statue of liberty in center
- Okada, Katsura
  - [Untitled], gold paint/text; 1640; 951; "he's got the whole world in his hands..."
- Okano, Haruko
  - [Untitled], passport in plastic; 1641; 803; Art booklet/passport The bio hazard bag is an integral part of the art
- Olaio, Antonio
  - [Untitled], 1642; 17; Submitted poem/image via email
- Olgiati, Eva
  - [Untitled], 1643; 534; Text computer screen images
- Olive, Frank
  - The History of Language - Chapter One: The Lowercase Letter L, text on paper; 1644; 728; A printed history of the lowercase letter L
- Olson, J Wayne
  - [Untitled], dye coupler print; 1645; 296; From the ? Series, "Question for a Fetus" Terror 911 2001
- Olson, Patricia
  - [Untitled], digital image; 1646; 1701; Group numbers 1701-1709; swirl in center
- Olson, Patricia
  - [Untitled], digital image; 1647; 1702; Group numbers 1701-1709; flag in hourglass
- Olson, Patricia
  - [Untitled], digital image; 1648; 1703; Group numbers 1701-1709; flag w/eagle
- Olson, Patricia
  - [Untitled], digital image; 1649; 1704; Group numbers 1701-1709; elongated people
- Olson, Patricia
  - [Untitled], digital image; 1650; 1705; Group numbers 1701-1709; fire hydrant
- Olson, Patricia
  - [Untitled], digital image; 1651; 1706; Group numbers 1701-1709; Osama, Bush
- Olson, Patricia
  - [Untitled], digital image; 1652; 1707; Group numbers 1701-1709; collage figure
- Olson, Patricia
  - [Untitled], digital image; 1653; 1708; Group numbers 1701-1709; squiggly lines
- Olson, Patricia
  - [Untitled], digital image; 1654; 1709; Group numbers 1701-1709; Please Help Me
- Ong, Diana
  - [Untitled], collage; 1655; 1444; Frederick Kuo
- Onishi, Nana
  - Bridge, 1656; 269
- Ono, Hitomi
  - Freedom amnd Peace to the Universe, 1657; 540; 1 of 2
- Ono, Hitomi
  - Freedon amnd Peace to the Universe, 1658; 539; 2 of 2
- Openshaw, Jonathan
  - The Day the Earth Stood III, 1659; 195
- Orbach, Nicki
  - [Untitled], text collage; 1660; 362
- Ortiz, Andrew J.
  - Console 2001, ink jet print; 1661; 784
- Ortiz, Lorri
  - Operation Brainstorm, 1662; 1220; Target
- Oshima, Seiji
  - Ars Cum Natura As Salutem Conspirat, text on paper; 1663; 1443; Bold black text on paper
- Osipinko, Ihna
  - [Untitled], pen on paper; 1664; 2059; Abstract line design
- Ospina, L.
  - Untitled, 1665; 2235; Imagine
- Ospina, Paula
  - [Untitled], 1666; 165; Print of rebar
- Ospina, Paula
  - [Untitled], 1668; 166; Flame
- Oste-Alexander, Pia
  - ...with the bodies..., collage and silver paint; 1669; 445
- Ostrom, Karen
  - The Filmmaker, a/p # 1; 1670; 561
- Otomo, Yuko
  - Season's Change (for Steve), 1671; 1719; Poems begins with "Jolted, my eyes see things differently"
- Ovelman
  - [Untitled], 1672; 1879; Guy hammering wall
- Owens, Jimmy
  - [Untitled], 1673; 1967; Open notebook
- Padilla
  - [Untitled], 1674; 1799
- Padin, Clemente
  - [Untitled], 1675; 3097; Mail art - envelope
- Padnos, Stella
  - 9 1 1, poem; 1676; 2184
- Palerado, Wayne
  - American Tear, 1677; Flag face
- Page, Bonnie
  - [Untitled], photograph; 1678; 1766; Wendy's, NY company
- Page, Judith
  - [Untitled], 1679; 273; "Sad truth; Mad Scramble; No Neutrality"
- Pailato, Laralanna
  - [Untitled], 1680; 845
- Palazzolo, Francis
  - [Untitled], 1681; 1675; "Neither the radical" rainbow.
- Pallares, William
  - "The New Towers", ink on paper; 1682; 1609; Interpretive drawing of WTC site with a handwritten list of reactions
- Pankin, Harris
  - Gostdance, 1683; 2018; Floating head
- Papageorge, Georgia
  - [Untitled], 1684; 74; Artwork sent via mail
- Parcher, Joyce
  - [Untitled], mixed media; 1685; 1474; Abstract painting of figures falling down page
- Pardee, Christy
  - [Untitled], 1686; 2034
- Park, Eung Ho
  - [Untitled], 1687; 535; Cut up metro cards
- Park, Eung Ho
  - [Untitled], 1688; 1797; Metrocard
- Park, Hunju
  - [Untitled], hair, color paper, and india ink; 1689; 1410; Dark mixed media
- Parkel, Sara
  - From the Victims of Violence, 1690; 1321; 8:45 and 9:03
- Parkel, Sara
  - 9:21 a.m. Port Authority of NY and NJ orders all bridges and tunnels in the NYC area closed..., print (letter picture); 1691; 1322; 9:43, 9:40, 9:21
- Parkel, Sara
  - [Untitled], 1692; 1324; 5:20
- Parkel, Sara
  - [Untitled], 1693; 1323; 10:28, 10:10, 10:05
- Parker, Karla
  - [Untitled], 1695; 257; Eagle with text over
- Pasco, Enric
  - 11 Septembre Global, digital image; 1696; 1933; Global
- Patino, Jose
  - Untitled 2001, scanned photographs printed with text; 1698; 1858; Three small photo's with text
- Patton, Amy
  - [Untitled], 1699; 1109
- Pavese, Erinn
  - [Untitled], 1700; 112; Artwork
- Pavkovic, Marija
  - [Untitled], 1701; 1994; Guess, Israel, Bosnian
- Pavlicovic, Jim
  - [Untitled], 1702; 573; "While they were building..."
- Pavone, Jessica
  - [Untitled], blank music sheet; 1703; 413
- Payne, Pam
  - Before and After Skyline, photographs; 1704; 1498; Two photographs w/man and woman sitting arranged vertically
- Paz, Hilda
  - Solo La Memoria, 1706; 2003
- Pearlman, Didra
  - [Untitled], text on paper; 1707; 2085; "Sins of the Father" (2085-2088)
- Pearlman, Didra
  - [Untitled], text on paper; 1708; 2086; "True Grief is..." (2085 - 2088)
- Pearlman, Didra
  - [Untitled], text on paper; 1709; 2087; "My joys are buried..." (2085 - 2088)
- Pearlman, Didra
  - [Untitled], text on paper; 1710; 2088; "I heard a child cry..." (2085 - 2088)
- Pechansky, Clara
  - The General and His Victims, watercolor; 1711; 265; Watercolor of large man in middle
- Pedley, Sue
  - Pray, do paper, watercolor to graph; 1712; 1058; 1 of 2
- Pedley, Sue
  - Glass House, xerox; 1713; 1059; 2 of 2
- Pelli, Leemour
  - [Untitled], 1714; 1628; Painted abstract figures in bottom half of paper
- Penaloza, Maricruz
  - [Untitled], comp print out; 1714b; 3264
- Penberg, David
  - Engaging in the World's Renewal Before Returning to Normalcy, 1715; 697; Text
- Pensato, Joyce
  - [Untitled], two photos; 1716; 853
- Perkins, Stephen
  - [Untitled], 1717; 494; Fear is the real terror
- Perkins, Stephen
  - [Untitled], 1718; 493; "I am sick of flags..."
- Perlman, C.
  - [Untitled], ink on paper; 1719; 992; Text on white paper "Need to live more truth fully! Now!"
- Perlstein, Tony
  - To the Workers of Windows on the World, 1720; 1843; Poem
- Perrier, Angelica
  - [Untitled], 1721; 3043; Exit Art -- Here is my submission for...
- Perrine, Doreen
  - [Untitled], 1722; 502; Drawing
- Perzynski, Bogdan
  - 2001 (Reactions), digital image; 1723; 1595; "we are not living..."
- Pesce, Rocco Anthony
  - [Untitled], digital image; 1724; 1936
- Pestov, Louri
  - [Untitled], 1725; 1958; Flag made of images of WTC
- Pestov, Louri
  - [Untitled], 1726; 3089; Flag with peace sign stars
- Pestov, Louri
  - [Untitled], 1727; 3090; Flag with peace sign stars and towers with thunderbolt...
- Pestov, Louri
  - [Untitled], 1728; 3091; Flag with peace sign stars and towers with thunderbolt and stars lower right...
- Pestov, Louri
  - [Untitled], 1729; 3092; Flag with peace sign stars and towers with thunderbolt no stars lower right...
- Petejan, Alisha
  - I only live here, 1730; 262; Image sent via email
- Petley, Kate
  - Nothing, mixed media on paper; 1731; 1493; Uneven line horizontial across vertical paper (1 of 2)
- Petley, Kate
  - Something, mixed media on paper; 1732; 1494; Two snowmen shapes at top of verticle paper (1 of 2)
- Petrick, Robert
  - [Untitled], 1733; 1612; Crucified Osama
- Petruska, John M.
  - I Just Got a Place in New York, text on paper; 1734; 1263; Short essay
- Peyton, Dan
  - [Untitled], 1735; 568; Line
- Pfeffer, Carol
  - [Untitled], 1736; 1429; Dark undefined image, arabic writing at top
- Pfeffer, Carol
  - [Untitled], 1737; 1427; Dark undefined image, arabic writing at top
- Pfeffer, Carol
  - [Untitled], 1738; 1424; Dark undefined image, square of arabic text in center
- Pfeffer, Carol
  - [Untitled], 1739; 1426; Dark undefined image, square of arabic text in center
- Phillips, Rachel
  - [Untitled], digital image; 1740; 787; Line drawing of an abstract explosion
- Piana, Petra
  - [Untitled], 1741; 538
- Piana, Petra
  - [Untitled], 1742; 537
- Pichardo, Jolie
  - [Untitled], text and photo; 1743; 1553; WTC
- Piegza, Richard
  - [Untitled], 1744; 116; Artwork via email
- Pinho, Carmen
  - [Untitled], 1745; 862
- Pinson, Nuala
  - I heard the words New York..., 1747; 2166
- Pinto, Mary
  - [Untitled], 1748; 1501
- Pischke, Erin
  - Candlelight Vigil, 1749; 370
- Platt, Liss
  - [Untitled], computer print out; 1750; 949; Tuesday
- Plaut, Melissa
  - [Untitled], photograph; 1751; 1026; Image of doors with McDonald's signs
- Plaza, F.
  - [Untitled], 1752; 1203; Figure
- Pleasants
  - [Untitled], 1754; 1823; Roller skate
- Plewinski, Maciej
  - [Untitled], photograph; 1755; 2112; Photo of twin towers and NYC skyline
- Plewinski, Maciej
  - [Untitled], photograph; 1756; 2111; Photo close-up of twin towers
- Plough, Jean
  - [Untitled], 1757; 260; Image of Bin Laden w/WTC background
- Pojrebniak, Vladimir
  - [Untitled], paper cut out attached with thread and glue; 1758; 939
- Ponsard, Nathalie Junod
  - [Untitled], 1759; 354; Black out partial image
- Porter, Bonnie
  - [Untitled], 1760; 1559; Black rectangle divided by a vertically line
- Porter, Carolyn A.